coolpad.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy - Coolpad : Coolpad

**Privacy Policy**

Coolpad.US is run and managed by Coolpad Technologies Inc. under China Wireless Group, which consists of Yulong Computer Telecommunication Scientific (Shenzhen) Co., LTD., Coolpad Communications Private Limited, and Coolpad Technologies Inc.

**Customer’s Privacy**

1\. GENERAL ASPECTS OF DATA COLLECTION AND USE

The privacy policy stipulated below (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to all online services directly provided by Coolpad Technologies, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“Coolpad”) These services are referred to collectively herein as the “Coolpad Services”. Coolpad is committed to protecting the online privacy of web visitors, users and customers of all of Coolpad Services.

This Privacy Policy is designed to advise you about the types of information we collect about you when you visit or submit information directly to Coolpad.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that you provide directly to third parties, including services or content you access via a Coolpad webpage.

You should always check the applicable privacy policy of any third party service providers whose service or content you access.

To the extent permitted by all applicable laws, including, without limitation, the Laws, rules and regulations of the People’s Republic of China (“Chinese Law”), and the Laws, rules and regulations of the United States of America, including its political subdivisions (collectively, “American Law”), Coolpad does not represent or warrant that Coolpad Services, or any part thereof, is appropriate, complete, accurate, or available for use in any specific jurisdiction.

If you choose to access Coolpad Services, you do so on your own initiative and at your own risk, and you alone are responsible for complying with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including, without limitation, Chinese Law and American Law.

As part of the Coolpad Services, you are given the chance to consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Failure to consent to such terms constitutes sufficient grounds for us to refuse access to the Coolpad Services in whole or in part, all is determined by us in our sole and complete discretion.

Your use and/or acceptance of all or any portion of the Coolpad Services shall be construed as your acceptance of all terms of this Privacy Policy in full, including, without limitation, the collection, disclosure, transfer, use, management and storage of “Personal Information”, as defined and described below. You understand and agree that Coolpad offers this service to the public in general and it is not reasonably feasible for Coolpad to enter into more specific agreements with consumers of the Coolpad Services, and that for the benefit of all, as well our protection from and against unwarranted liability, generally applicable rules must be applied and enforced.

From time to time Coolpad may transfer or merge any Personal Information collected off-line to its online databases or store off-line information in an electronic format.

This Privacy Policy covers all “Personal Information” and will remain in full force and effect as long the visitor uses all or any portion of the Coolpad Services, even if such visitor’s use of, or participation in, any particular service, feature, function or promotional activity terminates, expires, ceases, is suspended or deactivated for any reason.

Coolpad’s website, online services, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help Coolpad better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of the Coolpad Services have been accessed, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Coolpad treats information collected by cookies and other technologies as non Personal Information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information under applicable law, we also treat these identifiers as Personal Information. Similarly, to the extent that non-Personal Information is combined with Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

We use cookies and other technologies to remember Personal Information when you access Coolpad Services. If you want to disable cookies, check the features of your computer browser as well as the services offered by your Internet services provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note some of the Coolpad Services may not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We reserve the right to use this general information in designing our advertising and marketing services, but we are not obligated to do so. Notwithstanding, we will not use any Personal Information in connection with the design and developing of our advertising marketing services in any manner that discloses to the general public all or any portion of your Personal Information.

In some of our email messages, we may employ a “click-through URL” linked to some portion of the Coolpad Services. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.  

2\. INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT

Personal Information: In connection with your interaction with the Coolpad Services and submission of information to our website, including creation of a user name, completion of registration forms, responding to surveys and polls, registration of products, purchase of products, download of updates, and/or other use of the Coolpad Services, we may request that visitors supply us with Personal Information. Personal Information is specific and private information pertaining specifically to a particular individual and not designed for release to the general public, such as a name, mailing address, phone number, email address, home or work telephone number, contact preferences, and credit card information. The foregoing types of information are referred to herein as “Personal Information”.

We will make reasonable efforts to notify you when we are gathering Personal Information, and, other than incidentally in connection with the other activities described in this Privacy Policy, we will attempt to collect Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit it to us through our online forms and questionnaires, SMS text campaigns or through other voluntary on or offline means.

Although you obviously have no obligation to provide us with any information to use the Coolpad Services, you may not be able to fully utilize all of the features, files and locations that comprise the Coolpad Services if you choose not to provide certain information to us, all of which we, in our sole and complete discretion, determine. If, however, you do choose to give us Personal Information as part of your interaction with Coolpad Services, we will collect and retain that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Coolpad takes reasonable measures to ensure that the Personal Information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on visitors to update or correct Customer’s Personal Information whenever necessary. All users of Coolpad Service are required to provide true, current, complete and accurate Personal Information when prompted and we will reject and delete any entry that we believe in good faith to be incorrect, false, falsified, or fraudulent, or inconsistent with or in violation of the Privacy Policy, to the extent we are reasonably able to make such an evaluation in any particular instance. Neither the foregoing nor anything else herein shall require that we take any specific steps to verify or otherwise confirm that any information submitted to us by third parties is complete and/or accurate.

Non-Personal Information: When visitors use all or any portion of the Coolpad Services, we may also collect “non-Personal Information”. We consider “non-Personal Information” to be information that cannot be used to identify with specificity or contact visitors personally, such as demographic information, including, without limitation, education level, profession, zip code, interests, and the like. Non-Personal Information may also include technical information, such as Customer’s IP address and other anonymous data involving use of Coolpad Services. In addition, non-Personal Information may also include information that visitors provide us in the course of using the Coolpad Services, such as the terms visitors enter into the search functions of Coolpad Services and comments voluntarily left by them.

We reserve the right to use or disclose non-Personal Information pursuant to this Privacy Policy. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose certain information when, in our sole and complete discretion, we determine that such disclosure is necessary to protect us or our employees and other agents, the rights or property of any of the foregoing, or to protect the physical safety or health of our employees and/or any member or members of the general public.

Any submissions that visitors make to any public areas of the Site such as bulletin boards (“Public Areas”) will be public and will not be considered Personal Information under any circumstances. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of the Coolpad Services or of third parties with respect to any information visitors post in Public Areas. In addition, information that visitors submit to Public Areas may be collected and used by others to send visitors unsolicited messages and for other purposes. We have no obligation to prevent them from doing so.  

3\. SPECIFIC ASPECTS OF USE OF INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

Our Services

We use Personal Information to provide users of the Coolpad Services with any services that that may request or require, to communicate with visitors, and to allow visitors to participate in online surveys and publish the results thereof.

We use aggregated non-Personal Information about our users to understand our website’s demographics, such as the geographic distribution of our users, the number of users visiting a certain location, a combination of these and/or other demographics. We may also use the personal or non-personal information we collect to analyze how all or any portion of the Coolpad Services are being used, to improve the content of the Coolpad Services, and for marketing and promotional efforts, including direct marketing, so that we or any of our related companies can send users of the Coolpad Services information about products and services which we believe may be of interest to them.

E-mail Communications

If you e-mail us with questions or comments, we may use your Personal Information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. You also may be asked for consent to being contacted by e-mail, and for permission (either positively or by way of “opt out” procedures) to send you) information about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you, which e-mails may be sent either by us or by any of our related companies. You will have the opportunity to subscribe to an electronic newsletter that will send information about Coolpad Services or our advertisers to your e-mail address. However, we will provide you with the option to change your preferences and opt-out of receiving those communications.

4\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

Co-Branded Services and Features: Coolpad Services may also offer co-branded services and features, such as events and/or promotions that we put together with other companies or with one or more of our affiliated entities (each, a “Co-Branded Partner”). Such services and features may be hosted on our website and/or on our Co-Branded Partner’s website. We may share your Personal Information with our Co-Branded Partners and your voluntary use of, or participation in, a co-branded service or feature means that you “opt-in” and give your affirmative consent to both the provision of Coolpad Services and to permit our Co-Branded Partners to collect and use your Personal Information provided during the registration process and/or in connection with the specific co-branded feature or service for the fulfillment of the feature or service and for marketing or administrative purposes. If you wish to opt-out of a Co-Branded Partner’s future use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you will need to contact the Co-Branded Partner directly.

Business Transactions Involving Coolpad Services: As the Coolpad Services continue to develop, we may engage in commercial transactions such as buying, selling or combining the Coolpad Services with other businesses. In such case, non-Personal Information and Personal Information that we or other businesses have collected will likely be transferred as part of the transaction. If we engage in such a business, we will attempt to ensure that requests made to us regarding e-mail communications will be honored by relevant third parties to the extent that we are able to do so, but you understand that the disposition of such information may be beyond our reasonable control under such circumstances, and as part of the terms and conditions upon which provision of the Coolpad Services is conditioned both prior and subsequent, you waive all claims against us, our related individuals, and our related entities for any subsequent use of Personal Information by any other individual or entity who acquired such Personal Information from us, so long as we abided by the terms of this Privacy Policy while reasonably able to do so.

Third Party Advertisers

We may use third-party companies to deliver specific advertisements to visitors. These companies may collect non-Personal Information about your visits to our website and other use of the Coolpad Services in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you and/or other visitors or users. These companies may also aggregate Customer’s non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research, and other similar purposes. These companies may place their own cookies on your computer. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting and using this information, you must visit each third-party advertiser’s website directly and opt-out or otherwise comply with their rules regarding non-participation in such advertising and/or marketing efforts.

Other Disclosures

We may disclose Personal Information when we are required to do so under applicable law, when we are the subject of a court order, or when any law enforcement authority or regulatory agency which has jurisdiction to do so requests that we provide such Personal Information. We may also disclose Personal Information to the extent necessary to enforce our rights under law or pursuant to any agreement, or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves and our employees and other agents, the Coolpad Services, our users, and/or other third parties.

5\. CHILDREN

We ask that anyone under the age of thirteen not submit any Personal Information through the Coolpad Services. We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and therefore we do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under the age of 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as is reasonably possible under the circumstances. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we are not agreeing to conduct or undertake any specific measures to determine whether individual users are under the age of 13 years.

6\. SECURITY OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The security of all Personal Information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure Personal Information. However, please remember that there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically prior to our collection, and there are constant security risks associated with being interconnected, as well as criminal and other elements that seek to test electronic security measures and/or retrieve confidential data.

The Personal Information we collect is stored on databases that we control. We use security measures that we deem to be consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect some of the information in our possession, including Confidential Information. We restrict access to Personal Information to employees, contractors and/or other agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

7\. USER GENERATED CONTENT UPLOAD

Registered users that submit content to us agree to have certain Personal Information posted on our website as well as on any other platform on which we operate or provide services, or, if such feature is offered in connection with a Co-Branded Partner, on our Co-Branded Partner’s website. Registered users that upload videos may also be required to submit additional Personal Information and the videos may be screened for content and not posted if, in our sole and complete discretion, we believe that posting the video is in any way harmful to our interests or the interests of any third party.

Any submissions that you may make to any public areas of our website, such as postings to bulletin boards (“Public Areas”) will be public and will not be considered Personal Information.

We do not control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of the Site or of Clients with respect to any information visitors post in Public Areas. In addition, information that visitors submit to Public Areas may be collected and used by others to send visitors unsolicited messages and for other purposes.

8\. ARCHIVED INFORMATION

We maintain archives of its web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database. We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

9\. CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES

Registration may not always be required to enter promotions such as contests and sweepstakes. These may have a separate registration or entry processes. and participation therein may require you to submit Personal Information such as your first and last name, street address, city, state and zip code, e-mail address, telephone number and date of birth.

The entry page and/or rules of any contest will provide the specific requirements for the promotion involved. You may also have the opportunity to opt-in to special offers from our advertisers in connection with many of these types of promotions.

10\. ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy, the accuracy of Customer’s Personal Information or the use of Customer’s Personal Information, or any requests to access your information or that we correct, update, or remove Customer’s information in our databases, should be directed via e-mail to support@coolpad.com, or via regular mail to:

Coolpad Technologies, Inc.  
6175 Main Street, Suite 290  
Frisco, TX 75034  
Attention: Customer Support

If we receive written complaints at the address above, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. If we, in our sole and complete discretion, determine that it is appropriate to do so, we will work with regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data.

If you request that we change any of your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your Personal Information stored in databases that we actively use will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information removed from, or changed in, our active service databases. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our End User Terms and Conditions for the Application. Further, as a practical matter, it may not be technologically possible or commercially feasible to remove each and every record of information that visitors have provided to us, and by using all or any portion of the Coolpad Services, you waive all claims against us and any person or entitled acting on our behalf and/or related to us in any way, for any wrongful retention of any such information, whether the information is Personal Information or not.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 15, 2012, and complies with Coolpad’s Corporate Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole and complete discretion, but we will post any material changes to this Privacy Policy as soon as they go into effect. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

11\. ABOUT COOLPAD

Coolpad as used herein is a term used for convenience only that refers to Coolpad Technologies, Inc., a Delaware corporation, as well as all related entities and individuals, many of which are owned by or otherwise related to China Wireless Group. Notwithstanding the definition of this term, each of the foregoing entities is a separate and distinct legal entity, and no entity is authorized to or can accept or receive service of process on behalf of any other entity within the foregoing definition. No company within the China Wireless Group is legally liable for another unless specifically agreed to in writing or such liability is imposed by law. This site does not establish any nexus between any of the companies such that visitors can assume that they can be sued jointly or severally on behalf of another.

If visitors have any questions regarding this policy, please contact the Legal Department.

This privacy policy was last updated on August 21, 2012.
